yzi.me 2013-12-08

# Free Web Hosting - Privacy Policy

#### What information do we collect? 

We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.  
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days. 

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

#### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

#### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at <http://www.2freehosting.com/tos.html>

#### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

info@2freehosting.com
